1. openBrowser
2. maximizeWindow
3. navigateToUrl
4. setText
5. setText
6. setText
7. setText
8. setText
9. setText
10. Statement - excelInfo = ["fname":"", "lname":"", "pgender":"", "pday":"", "pmonth":"", "pyear":""]
11. Statement - rawData = com.kms.katalon.core.testdata.TestDataFactory.findTestData("Data Files/WB_Primo/Passenger_details")
12. Statement - excelRowNo = rawData.getRowNumbers()
13. Statement - randomPaxIndex = 1
14. waitForElementClickable
15. Statement - driver = com.kms.katalon.core.webui.driver.DriverFactory.getWebDriver()
16. Statement - roomContainerXpath = "id("booking")/div[@class="wrapper second-bg"]/div[contains(@class,"container-mx")]/div[@class="row"]/div[@class="col-md-12 roomContainer"]"
17. Statement - roomsCount = driver.findElements(org.openqa.selenium.By.xpath(roomContainerXpath)).size()
18. Statement - println("roomsCount=" + roomsCount)
19. Statement - For ([i = 1, i <= roomsCount, (i++)])
20. scrollToElement
21. Done so that click on \"Next\" button is possible for Mobile env.\r\nClick on total so Keyboard area gets closed.
22. scrollToElement
23. waitForElementClickable
24. waitForElementVisible
25. scrollToElement
26. click
27. scrollToElement
28. waitForElementPresent
29. waitForElementVisible
30. waitForElementClickable
31. click
32. Select default travel insurance\r\n
33. Click on individual pax insurance selection checkbox
34. scrollToElement
35. click
36. scrollToElement
37. waitForElementVisible
38. Click on individual pax insurance selection checkbox
39. scrollToElement
40. waitForElementClickable
41. Click on first product category \"Individual choices\" radio button
42. scrollToElement
43. Click on first product category \"Yes please\" checkbox, so all passengers get default product in category
44. scrollToElement
45. Scroll to Accept terms checkbox LABEL
46. Click on to Accept terms checkbox LABEL
47. Scroll to Accept terms checkbox
48. Click on to Accept terms checkbox
49. scrollToElement
50. waitForElementClickable
51. Click on save booking.
52. Wait for booking to be placed, max 30 seconds