1. openBrowser
2. maximizeWindow
3. navigateToUrl
4. setText
5. setText
6. setText
7. setText
8. setText
9. setText
10. setText
11. setText
12. scrollToElement
13. Done so that click on \"Next\" button is possible for Mobile env.\r\nClick on total so Keyboard area gets closed.
14. scrollToElement
15. waitForElementClickable
16. waitForElementVisible
17. scrollToElement
18. click
19. waitForElementPresent
20. click
21. Select default travel insurance\r\n
22. Click on individual pax insurance selection checkbox
23. scrollToElement
24. click
25. scrollToElement
26. waitForElementVisible
27. Click on individual pax insurance selection checkbox
28. scrollToElement
29. Click on first product category \"Individual choices\" radio button
30. scrollToElement
31. Click on first product category \"Yes please\" checkbox, so all passengers get default product in category
32. scrollToElement
33. Scroll to Accept terms checkbox LABEL
34. Click on to Accept terms checkbox LABEL
35. Scroll to Accept terms checkbox
36. Click on to Accept terms checkbox
37. scrollToElement
38. waitForElementClickable