1. openBrowser
2. maximizeWindow
3. navigateToUrl
4. waitForPageLoad
5. scrollToElement
6. waitForElementClickable
7. click
8. click
9. Click search on Primotours.dk
10. waitForPageLoad
11. waitForElementClickable
12. scrollToElement
13. waitForElementVisible
14. waitForElementClickable
15. scrollToElement
16. Click \"Book\" on Primotours.dk offer
17. switchToWindowTitle
18. setText
19. setText
20. setText
21. setText
22. setText
23. setText
24. setText
25. setText
26. scrollToElement
27. waitForElementClickable
28. waitForElementVisible
29. click
30. waitForElementPresent
31. click
32. Select default travel insurance\r\n
33. Click on individual pax insurance selection checkbox
34. scrollToElement
35. click
36. scrollToElement
37. waitForElementVisible
38. Click on individual pax insurance selection checkbox
39. scrollToElement
40. Click on first product category \"Individual choices\" radio button
41. scrollToElement
42. Click on first product category \"Yes please\" checkbox, so all passengers get default product in category
43. scrollToElement
44. Scroll to Accept terms checkbox LABEL
45. Click on to Accept terms checkbox LABEL
46. Scroll to Accept terms checkbox
47. Click on to Accept terms checkbox
48. scrollToElement
49. waitForElementClickable
50. Click on save booking.
51. closeBrowser