1. openBrowser
2. navigateToUrl
3. waitForElementClickable
4. click
5. click
6. click
7. waitForElementClickable
8. scrollToElement
9. click
10. switchToWindowTitle
11. setText
12. setText
13. setText
14. setText
15. setText
16. setText
17. setText
18. setText
19. scrollToElement
20. waitForElementClickable
21. waitForElementVisible
22. click
23. waitForElementPresent
24. click
25. Select default travel insurance\r\n
26. Click on individual pax insurance selection checkbox
27. scrollToElement
28. click
29. scrollToElement
30. waitForElementVisible
31. Click on individual pax insurance selection checkbox
32. scrollToElement
33. Click on first product category \"Individual choices\" radio button
34. scrollToElement
35. Click on first product category \"Yes please\" checkbox, so all passengers get default product in category
36. scrollToElement
37. Scroll to Accept terms checkbox LABEL
38. Click on to Accept terms checkbox LABEL
39. Scroll to Accept terms checkbox
40. Click on to Accept terms checkbox
41. scrollToElement
42. waitForElementClickable
43. Click on save booking.
44. closeBrowser